Guide to the Oral History of the American Left Collection OH.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV. Filmmakers' Tapes and Transcripts
  - Peekskill Riot, 1979-1980
    - Mercadel, Kevin, February 27, 1979; cuid1053
      Original Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 57 min.
      - Access Copy (Box 30, Cd cuid1053)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0023)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Minter, Bernie -- Transcript, September 17, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Moliti, Vito, February 18, 1980
      - Access Copy (Box 84, Audiocassette 132)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0067)
    - Moscow, Warren, undated
      - Access Copy (Box 75, Audiocassette 47)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0013)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Naison, Mark, March 2, 1979
      - Access Copies (Box 85, Audiocassette 30A, 30C)
      - Seminar Transcript (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Naylor, Colin, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 85, Audiocassette 14)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 195, Audiocassette 002.0120)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Neuchow, Bill and Bill Taylor, January 9, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 75, Audiocassette 60A)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0074)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Okun, Nan -- Transcript, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Olson, Jesse and George Goodman, August 28-29, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 75, Audiocassette 61)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0073)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Osheroff, Abe -- Transcript, undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Overstreet, Fred, October 23, 1979
      - Access Copies (Box 75, Audiocassette 74A-74B)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0093)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 195, Audiocassette 002.0119)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Patterson, Bill and Louise, January 10, 1979; cuid43077
      - Access Copy, cuid43077A (Box 75, Audiocassette cuid43077A)
        Duration: 75 minutes; Preservation Note: Side 2 is blank.
      - Access Copy, cuid43077B (Box 75, Audiocassette cuid43077B)
        Duration: 75 minutes.
      - Original Audio Recordings (Box Shared Tamiment 195, Audiocassette 002.0117-002.0118)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Payne, Anita, May 5, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 82, Audiocassette 89)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0007)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Peery, Nelson, August 20, 1980
      - Access Copy (Box 84, Audiocassette 127A)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0040)
    - Peterson, Caleb -- Transcript, undated (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Phoner, Phil -- Transcript, November 30, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Poritzky, Ben, October-December 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 75, Audiocassette 76)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0063)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Rauch, Mrs. -- Transcript, December 30, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Reibman, Svi, March 7, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 82, Audiocassette 104)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0083)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Resnick, Ephraim, June 28, 1979 (Box 84, Audiocassette 126)
      - Access Copy (Box 84, Audiocassette 126)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0076)
    - Rick, Chester R., August 3, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 82, Audiocassette 78)
      - Interview Summary (Box 70, Folder 19)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0052)
    - Rock, Pauline, undated
      - Access Copy (Box 82, Audiocassette 105)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0003)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Rosen, Helen -- Transcript, undated (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Rosen, Judy -- Transcript, undated (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Rossmar, Barbara, February 15, 1972
      - Access Copy (Box 82, Audiocassette 106)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0046)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Rowe, Billy, May 2, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 75, Audiocassette 48)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0012)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Rubenfeld, Leonard -- Transcript, January 15, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Russo, Sandra -- Transcript, February 6, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Salzberg, Norman and Dan, undated
      - Access Copies (Box 82, Audiocassette 114A-114B)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0036)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0077)
    - Saroff, Sophia -- Transcript, February 7, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Schiller, Herb -- Transcript, April 3, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Schwartz, Goldie and Walter, 1979
      - Access Copies (Box 82, Audiocassette 109A-109B)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0045)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0088)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Schwartz, Tony, January 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 84, Audiocassette 117)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45)
    - Scivoletto, John, October 27, 1979 or 1980 (Box 84, Audiocassette 120)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0041)
    - Script Meetings, 1979
      - Access Copies -- January (Box 84, Audiocassette 125N-125Q)
      - Access Copies -- February (Box 84, Audiocassette 125J, 125M)
      - Access Copies -- March (Box 84, Audiocassette 125A-125I)
      - Access Copies -- April (Box 84, Audiocassette 125R)
      - Access Copy -- Undated (Box 84, Audiocassette 125L)
      - Original Audio Recordings -- January (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0081, 002.0098-002.0099)
      - Original Audio Recordings -- February (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0080, Box 56, Audiocassette 002.0085)
        Original recording 002.0085 is damaged.
      - Original Audio Recordings -- March (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0037, 002.0056, Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0079)
      - Original Audio Recordings -- April (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0054)
      - Original Audio Recordings -- November (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0082, 002.0084)
      - Original Audio Recordings -- Undated (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0055, 002.0058)
    - Seeger, Pete and Toshi, January 23-24, 1979
      - Access Copies (Box 85, Audiocassette 24A-24B)
      - Original Audio Recordings (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0033-002.0034)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Segal, Edith -- Interview Summary (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Selnick, Teckla -- Interview Summary, undated (Box 70, Folder 33)
    - Shappes, Morris, undated
      - Access Copy (Box 82, Audiocassette 111)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0087)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 34)
    - Shields, Art, undated
      - Access Copy (Box 84, Audiocassette 128)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0065)
    - Shikes, Ralph, January 16, 1980
      - Access Copy (Box 75, Audiocassette 39)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0019)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Siegel, Jeff, February 16, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 85, Audiocassette 32A)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0105)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Silber, Irwin, February 23, 1979; cuid43164
      Preservation note: Poor audio quality
      - Access Copy (Box 85, Audiocassette 26)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0031)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Silber, Sylvia, December 2, 1972; cuid43163
      - Access Copy (Box 85, Audiocassette 25)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0032)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Silverman, Sol, July and September 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 75, Audiocassette 8A)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0071)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0091)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 39)
    - Singer, Lou -- Transcript, November 27, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 40)
    - Slochower, Dr., March 19, 1979
      - Access Copies (Box 84, Audiocassette 124A-124B)
      - Original Audio Recordings (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0097, 002.0102)
    - Slutsky, Samuel -- Transcript, May 12, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Coleman, May 5, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 82, Audiocassette 81)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0062)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 42)
    - Steck, Bob, undated
      - Access Copy (Box 82, Audiocassette 112)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 48, Audiocassette 002.0044)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 43)
    - Stolley, Richard, 1979-1980
      - Access Copy (Box 75, Audiocassette 49)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0006)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 44)
    - Stovall, Ellen -- Original Audio Recording, undated (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0094)
    - Strauss, Leon, January 2, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 45)
    - Suller, Elsie and Madeline Simon -- Transcript, undated (Box 70, Folder 46)
    - Sverdlow, Amy, undated
      - Access Copy (Box 82, Audiocassette 116)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0003)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 47)
    - Tabb, Bill, March 15, 1979
      - Access Copies (Box 85, Audiocassette 33A-33B)
      - Original Audio Recordings (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0021-002.0022)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 48)
    - Tapley, Mel, January 16, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 85, Audiocassette 50)
      - Interview Summary (Box 70, Folder 49)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box 45, Audiocassette 002.0005)
    - Tarantel, Al, January 24, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 85, Audiocassette 10)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 195, Audiocassette 002.0122)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 50)
    - Tomkins, Tommy -- Transcript (Box 70, Folder 51)
    - Tommy, 1979 (Box 56, Audiocassette 002.0114)
    - Tuttle, Jack, October 23, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 85, Audiocassette 18)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 195, Audiocassette 002.0113)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 52)
    - Unidentified Access Copy, undated (Box 84, Audiocassette 130)
    - Unidentified Access Copy, undated (Box 84, Audiocassette 131)
    - Unidentified Original Audio Recording, undated (Box 49, Audiocassette 002.0095)
    - Walsh, John, 1979
      - Access Copy (Box 85, Audiocassette 19)
      - Original Audio Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 195, Audiocassette 002.0112)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 53)
    - Ward, Doug, January 16, 1979; cuid1052
      Origial Format: 1/8" Audiocassette, Duration: 20 min.
      - Access Copy (Box 30, Cd cuid1052)
      - Access Copy (Box 85, Audiocassette 34)
      - Transcript (Box 70, Folder 54)
    - White, Algernon -- Transcript, October 11, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 55)
  - The Wobblies
    - Film Transcript and Publicity Materials, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - List of Transcripts, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Abrams, Irving -- Transcript, July 11, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Baldwin, Roger -- Transcript, June 15, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Carlson, Grace and Dorothy Schultz -- Transcript, May 1, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Cedervall, Frank -- Transcript, July 8, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Cedervall, Mrs. -- Transcript, July 8, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Cohen, Sophie -- Transcript, December 17, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Fair, James -- Transcript, December 21, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Foudi, Mike -- Transcript, July 19, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Hansen, Irv -- Transcript, July 15, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - The Kongas -- Transcript, October 1978 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Krieger, Sam -- Transcript, September 24, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Lombardi, Irma -- Transcript, undated (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Melman, Phil -- Transcript, April 30, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Mignone, Dominic -- Transcript, April 17, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Miller, Jack -- Transcript, February 21, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Murphy, Joe -- Transcript, September 23, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Nurse, Art -- Transcript, July 14, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Petersen, Nels -- Transcript, February 23, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Petersen, Nels and Utah Phillips -- Transcript, undated (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Pfaff, Henry -- Transcript, July 7, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Phillips, Utah -- Transcript, February 25, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Pintek, Mrs. -- Transcript, July 19, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Rocco, Angelou -- Transcript, undated (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Scribner, Tom -- Transcript, April 29, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Shields, Art -- Transcript, undated (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Steelink, Nicholas -- Transcript, July 17, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Thompson, Fred -- Transcript, July 9, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Film Transcripts
    - Miles of Smiles, Years of Struggle -- Transcript, Reel Inventory, and List of Participants, 1978-1981 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - With Babies and Banners: Story of Women's Emergency Brigade -- Transcript, Brochure, and Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Eugene Debs Interview Transcript -- Unidentified Documentary, undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Grace and James Boggs Show -- Show #208 with Ossie and Ruby -- Transcript, circa 1982-1983 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Columbia Student Strike of 1968, undated; cuid1601
    This subseries contains eight interviews regarding the 1968 student strike at Columbia University.
- Series V. Tamiment Institute Tapes, circa 1955-1965
  This series contains a collection of tapes held by the Tamiment Institute that predated the establishment of the Oral History of the American Left. These tapes include recordings of meetings, speeches, panel discussions, and interviews recorded during the 1950s-1960s.
  - Bohn, Frank -- Original Audio Recording, March 1958; cuid1603 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0224)
    Recording regarding the Socialist Party, the Industrial Workers of the World from 1900-1920, and the church and socialism.
  - Brazier, Dick, et al. -- "Memorial Meeting", November 18, 1960
    - Access Copies (Box 83, Audiocassette 1A-1D)
    - Original Audio Recordings (Box 89, Audiocassette 1A-1D)
  - Call Association, undated; cuid1604; 3 sound tape reels 1/4"
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 45 min.
    - Original Audio Recordings (Box 55, Quarter inch audio reel cuid1604A, cuid1604B, cuid1604C)
  - Clarence and Ruth Senior on Norman Thomas, February 4, 1962; cuid1609
    - Access Copy (Box 83, Audiocassette 11)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 89, Audiocassette 11)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0213)
  - Fleischman, Harry Regarding Norman Thomas, April 23, 1964; cuid1605
    Harry Fleischman on Norman Thomas: A Biography.
    - Access Copy (Box 83, Audiocassette 8)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 89, Audiocassette 8)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0214)
  - Industrial Workers of the World, April 11, 1959; cuid1606
    Tamiment Institute discussion, including a memorial meeting featuring speakers Dick Brazier, Herbert Mahler, and Sam Weiner.
    - Access Copy (Box 83, Audiocassette 13A-13B)
    - Original Audio Recordings (Box 89, Audiocassette 13A-13B)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0215, 002.0212)
  - Industrial Workers of the World -- Finances and Decline -- Unidentified IWW Representative, circa 1950-1960
    - Access Copy (Box 83, Audiocassette 14)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 89, Audiocassette 14)
  - Panken, Judge Jacob, June 21, 1960; cuid1607
    Recording regarding Meyer London.
    - Access Copy (Box 83, Audiocassette 2)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 89, Audiocassette 2)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0126)
  - Randolph, A. Philip, undated; cuid1608
    Recording of a speech.
    - Access Copy (Box 83, Audiocassette 3)
    - Original Audio Recording, cuid43202 (Box 89, Audiocassette 3)
      Duration: 16 minutes
    - Original Audio Recordings (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0221-002.0223)
  - Shactman, Max -- Original Audio Recording, December 31, 1966; cuid1610 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0218)
    Recording of a speech titled "The Social Development of Communism."
  - Sinclair, Upton, October 15, 1958; cuid1611
    Speech at a League for Industrial Democracy Meeting.
    - Access Copy (Box 83, Audiocassette 4)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 89, Audiocassette 4)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0227)
  - Souchy, Antonin, February 29, 1960; cuid1612
  - Tamiment Discussion with the Children of Norman Thomas, 1959; cuid1615
    - Access Copies (Box 83, Audiocassette 7A-7B)
    - Original Audio Recordings (Box 89, Audiocassette 7A-7B)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0215-002.0216)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1956-1964; cuid1613
    - Access Copy, November 14, 1956 (Box 83, Audiocassette 10)
    - Original Audio Recording, November 14, 1956 (Box 89, Audiocassette 10)
    - Access Copies, 1964 (Box 83, Audiocassette 9A-9B)
    - Original Audio Recordings, 1964 (Box 89, Audiocassette 9A-9B)
    - Original Audio Recording, 1964 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0226)
  - Trachtenberg, undated
    - Access Copy (Box 83, Audiocassette 5)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 89, Audiocassette 5)
  - Walling, Anna Strunsky, June-July 1960; cuid1616
    This interview was originally taken as part of a Tamiment Institute oral history series.
    Interview by Melvin Drimmer and Melvyn Dubofsky.
    - Access Copy (Box 25, Cd Walling 1-4)
    - Access Copies (Box 83, Audiocassette 12A-12B)
    - Original Audio Recordings (Box 89, Audiocassette 12A-12B)
    - Original Audio Recordings (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0219-002.0220)
  - Weiner, Sam -- Original Audio Recording, 1962; cuid1617 (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0225)
    Recording regarding the Industrial Workers of the World from a WCKR Broadcast.
  - Wolfe, Bertram, July 12, 1960; cuid1618
    Recording of a speech titled "Has the Soviet Union Changed?"
    - Access Copy (Box 83, Audiocassette 6)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 89, Audiocassette 6)
    - Original Audio Recording (Box 42, Quarter inch audio reel 002.0217)
- Series VI. Aleine Austin Tapes regarding Monthly Review and Highlander Folk School, 1979-1982; cuid1619
  The Tennessee-based Highlander Folk School was founded in 1932 to provide education to activist leaders.
  Monthly Review is a socialist magazine founded in 1949.
  This series contains recordings of interviews by Aleine Austin and an event regarding the history of the Monthly Review.
  - Austin, Aleine, undated; cuid44746
    - Tape 1 -- Original Recording, cuid44752 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44752)
      Duration: 92 min; Preservation Note: This recording has muddy audio.
    - Tape 2 -- Original Recording, cuid44753 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44753)
      Duration: 79 min; Preservation Note: This recording has muddy audio.
    - Tape 3 -- Original Recording, cuid44754 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44754)
      Duration: 49 min; Preservation Note: This recording has muddy audio.
    - Access Copies (Box 88, Audiocassette 8A-8C)
    - Transcripts (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Blankfort, Michael, July 22, 1981; cuid44742
    - Original Recording, cuid44756 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44756)
      Duration: 90 min
    - Access Copy (Box 88, Audiocassette 11)
  - Edelman, Harburg, May, December 7, 1980; cuid44741
    - Original Recording, cuid44757 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44757)
      Duration: 25 min
    - Access Copy (Box 88, Audiocassette 6)
  - Former Harvard Student, December 10, 1980; cuid44744
    - Original Recording, cuid44755 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44755)
      Duration: 22 min; Preservation Note: Side 2 of the tape is blank
    - Access Copy (Box 88, Audiocassette 4)
    - Transcripts (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Horton, Magdoff, Ortiz, Sweezy, June 28, 1983; cuid44739
    - Original Recording, cuid44758 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44758)
      Duration: 91 min
    - Access Copy (Box 88, Audiocassette 3)
  - Horton, Myles, August 18-24, 1982
    - Original Recordings (Box 88, Audiocassette 2A-2F)
    - Access Copies (Box 88, Audiocassette 2A-2F)
  - Magdoff, Ortiz, Sweezy, undated; cuid44743
    - Tape 1 -- Original Recording, cuid44747 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44747)
      Duration: 64 min; Preservation Note: Audio is very poor.
    - Tape 2 -- Original Recording, cuid44748 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44748)
      Duration: 45 min
    - Access Copies (Box 88, Audiocassette 1A-1B)
    - Transcripts (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Review 30th Anniversary, May 1979; cuid44745
    - Tape 1 -- Original Recording, cuid44749 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44749)
      Duration: 82 min
    - Tape 2 -- Original Recording, cuid44750 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44750)
      Duration: 61 min
    - Access Copies (Box 88, Audiocassette 7A-7B)
    - Transcripts (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Sweezy, Paul, October 23, 1983; cuid44740
    - Original Recording, cuid44751 (Box 88, Audiocassette cuid44751)
      Duration: 35 min
    - Access Copy (Box 88, Audiocassette 5)
  - Thrasher, Sue -- Transcript, August 19, 1982; TW_OH_002_ER_1
- Series VII. Restricted Interviews in Oral History of the American Left, 1976-1983
  This series contains interviews collected for the Oral History of the American Left that were accepted by the repository as closed, generally for a certain amount of years. The majority of these restrictions are no longer in effect. Upon expiration of restrictions, interviews have been moved to Series I.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access to interviews in this series is restricted. Interviews for which restrictions have expired have been moved to Series 1. Specific information on the restrictions is available at the interview level. Please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu for more information.
  - Ewen, Stuart and Elizabeth, Nov. 7, 1983; cuid1621
    Interview is closed, except with the permission of the interviewees.
    - Access Copies (Box 91, Audiocassette 1, 2, 2B)
    - Original Audio Recordings (Box 90, Audiocassette 6A-6B)
  - Stern, Charlotte, 1976-1979
    - Access Copies, 1976 (Box 91, Audiocassette 1A, 1B, 2, 3A, 3B, 4B, 4D, 5B, 6)
    - Original Audio Recordings, 1976 (Box 90, Audiocassette 7A-7M)
    - Transcripts, 1976-1979 (Box 43, Folder 1-7)
  - Interviews by Alan Wald -- Original Audio Recordings, 1976-1981; cuid1622 (Box 90, Audiocassette 1-4, 8A-11B)
    Interviews by Alan Wald on the history of Trotskyism and intellectuals in the United States. Interviewees include Michael Blankfort (Jul 22, 1981), James T. Farrell (May 23, 1976), Leslie Fiedler (May 28, 1981), Nathan Glazer (May 25, 1981), Walter Goldwater (May 10, 1981), and Stan Weir (Sep 26, 1980 and Jul 21, 1981).
    Interview is closed.
- Series VIII. Higley Hill, 2009; cuid1623
  - Access Copy (Box 47, Cd Higley Hill)
- Series IX. Rose Leopold, 2008; cuid1624
  - Leopold, Rose
    - Access Copy (Box 47, Cd Rose Leopold)
    - Original Audio Recordings, November 1995 (Box 46, Audiocassette 02.9-001, 02.9-002, 02.9-003, 02.9-004, 02.9-005, 02.9-006. 02.9-007)
    - Transcripts, November 1995 (Box 46, Folder 3-8)
  - Malbin, Virginia
    - Access Copies, February-May 2008 (Box 46, Cd 02.9-008-01-02; 02.9-009-01; 02.9-010-01-02; 02.9-011-01; 02.9-012.01; 02.9-013-01-02; 02.9-014-01-02; 02.9-015-01-02)
    - Interview Transcript, February 13, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Notebook, August-September 1937 (Box 46, Folder 1)